# **Andres Maneiro**

# Soporte Técnico / Front-End Developer

amaneiro7@gmail.com +58 414-662-7870 Urb Monte Claro Sector Casa M6, 4005, Maracaibo, Venezuela (Bolivarian Republic of) 34 years old | Venezuelan



### PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

Experienced and professional IT support with over than ten years of valuable experience in issue resolution, customer service, projects effective execution to guarantee the success of the company. Familiar and adept at working with engineering, change control management, and business transformation systems. Accustomed to handling IT support, managing IT projects and supporting various engineering departments with IT tools and applications. Develop a motivated attitude and the ability to establish solid and productive relationships with other members of the company.

I am currently a student at Platzi and I want to start a career as a Front-End developer. I have skills in HTML,CSS, SASS, TailwindCSS, JavaScript, React and NodeJS

# PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

### Jun 2018 - Present Especialista Senior - Banco Nacional de Credito

Maracaibo, Venezuela

- Soporte a usuario
- Mantenimiento Preventivo y correctivo
- Colaborar con el equipo TI para asegurar que el software de seguraridad fue instalado correctamente en todo los equipos de los empleados.
- Experiencia en trabajo remoto
- Trabajo con WIndows Server, VMWare and VirtualBox
- Uso de herramientas como System Center Configuration Manager y HP Service Manager

### Sep 2011 - Feb 2018 Analista en Soporte Técnico Nivel II - Universidad Dr. Jose Gregorio Hernandez (UJGH)

Maracaibo, Venezuela

- Soporte a usuarios.
- Mantenimiento preventivo y correctivo de computadoras
- Reparación de monitores y computadoras.

#### May 2010 - Jan 2011 Técnico POS - Cooperativa IT & Services

Maracaibo, Venezuela

- Mantenimiento preventivo y correctivo de Punto de Ventas
- Instalación y configuración.
- Actualizacion de Sistama operativo e instalación de Aplicativos.

#### Feb 2009 - Sep 2009 Asistente - Centro de diagnistico y adistramiento automotriz Amaya Cars

Maracaibo, Venezuela

- Asistente en la reparación eléctrica y electrónica de automóviles.
- Manejo básico del scanner
- Reparación de cableado interno.

#### May 2008 - Feb 2009 Encargado - Inversiones Jocal (Cyber)

Maracaibo. Venezuela

- Mantenimiento preventivo y correctivo de computradoras.
- Soporte a usuarios

#### May 2008 - Jul 2008 Pasantías - Científica Industrial Venezuela

Maracaibo, Venezuela

- Mantenimiento preventivo y correctivo de equipos médicos.
- Soporte a usuarios.

### **SKILLS**

Soporte Ténico

System Center Configuration Manager

HP Service Manager

**Active Directory** 

Windows Server

Resolución de conflictos

HTML

21.00

JavaScript

TailwindCSS

React Node

**VMWare** 

API Rest

CSS

Git

SASS

Microsoft Azure

MySQL PostgresSQL

# **EDUCATION**

2000 - 2005

Bachiller en Ciencias

Maracaibo, Venezuela U.E. Instituto Experimental Cantaclaro

2006 - 2009

Técnico Superior Universitario en Electrónica

Maracaibo, Venezuela Colegio Universitario Rafael Belloso Chacín (CUNIBE)

### **LANGUAGES**

Spanish: Native speaker English: Intermediate - CEVAZ

# **LINKS**

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/amaneiro7/

Twitter: @andruelectronic Instagram: @amaneiro7 Facebook: @amaneiro7

Github: https://github.com/amaneiro7 Portfolio: https://amaneiro7.github.io/

### **HOBBIES**

Football, PowerLifting

### **COURSES**

Mantenimiento y reparación de computadoras - CEFAE - 2007

Azure Fundamentals - Microsoft - 2022

Full Stack Observability - New Relic - 2023

HTML and CSS - PLATZI - 2022

JavaScript - PLATZI - 2022

# **REFERRALS**

Noaly Delgado

Coordinadora - Banco Nacional de Credito

ndelgado@bnc.com.ve

+58 412-069-5936

Johanna Olivares

Gerente - Banco Nacional de Credito

jolivares@bnc.com.ve

+58 412-652.7977